[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":51470,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":58488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7186,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":65678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":12478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":78159,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2818,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":80981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":86013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1895,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":87908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one  to it. I f the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":91943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2154,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":94099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":98783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1599,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":100384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4044,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":104430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct!  3 +<sub >6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1077,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":105509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":109510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1556,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":111069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub>  3? <br  /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2888,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":113958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1295,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":115254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get  your re sult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4418,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":119673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1195,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":120870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":124092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1048,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":125141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":129190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":902,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":130094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":14851,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":144951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its  own inv erse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":31437,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":176390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":183157,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2039,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":185197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub >? <br / ><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3281,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":188479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1260,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":189742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":192566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1049,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":193617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3850,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":197469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identi ty under  +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1162,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":198632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":15044,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":213679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5237,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":218918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation  can simp ly be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":50621,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":269541,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<s ub>6</su b> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":63617,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":333160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":30576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":363737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1974,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":365714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":372026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":59668,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":431695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<s ub>6</su b>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":40896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":472592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2612,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":475207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":8105,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":483312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3326,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":486640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedba ck to ma ke sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":21160,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":507802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":9950,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":517754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2117,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":519872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":7068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":526944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":531719,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":534944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5973,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":540919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":544343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":8935,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":553280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subtract anything.","explanation_history":["Four add","Four ad","Four a","Four plus one is five and sen","Four plus one is five and se","Four plus one is five and s","Four plus one is five and ","Four plus one is five and","Four plus one is five an","Four plus one is five a","Four plus one is five ","Four plus one is five","Four plus one is five. Since it is no ","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight I ","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight I","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight ","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subract any","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to sub ract an","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subract a","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subract ","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subract","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subrac","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subra","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subr","Four plus one is five. Since it is not greater than eight, there is no need to subtract anything."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":59703,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":612986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"Eight p lus four is twelve. Since it is greater than eight, I subtracted nine. Twelve minus nine is three.","explanation_history":["Eight plus four is twelve. Since it is greater than eight ","Eight plus four is twelve. Since it is greater than eight, I subrtracted nine. Twelve minus nine is ","Eight plus four is twelve. Since it is greater than eight, I subtracted nine. Twelve minus nine is three."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":43395,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":656383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"Zero added to any number is itself.","explanation_history":["Zero added to any number is itself."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":32099,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":688484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":6976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":695461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":13280,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":708742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8303,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":717047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I add six to three, I get nine. Nine minus nine is zero, which is the identity.","explanation_history":["Nine mu","Nine minys ","Nine minys","Nine miny","Nine minus three is z","Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I ad ","Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I add six to three, I get nine. Nine mu","Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I add six to three, I get nine. Nine minus nine is zero, th","Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I add six to three, I get nine. Nine minus nine is zero, t","Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I add six to three, I get nine. Nine minus nine is zero, ","Nine minus three is six. Thus, if I add six to three, I get ni ne. Nine  minus nine is zero, which is the identity."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":59877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":776925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By continuing to add twos, I can get three, five and seven.","explanation_history":["Thw","Th","T","I can get two, four ","I can get two, four, six, and eigh","I can get two, four, six, and eigt","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding two, ","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding two,","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. ONce ","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos.  ONce"," I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. ONc","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. ON","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. One ","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. One","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. On","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. O","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. ONc","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. ON","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. O","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subrtr","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subrt","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subr","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I t","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. Wh en I add  five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By adding more twos to one I can ","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By adding","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By ","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By continuing to add tow","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By continuing to add to","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By continuing to add twos, I g","I can get two, four, six, and eight by ad ding two s. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By continuing to add twos, I can get three, five and","I can get two, four, six, and eight by adding twos. When I add five twos, I get ten. Subtract nine, since ten is more than eight, and I get one. By continuing to add twos, I can get three, five and seven."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":208419,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":985345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zero. Then the pattern repeats. You can only get zero, three, and six.","explanation_history":["I","If ","If","I","Three","Thre","Thr","Th","T","I a"," I can get three and six","I can get three and si","I can get three and s","I can get three and ","I can get three and","I can get three an","I can get three a","I can get three and se","I can get three and sis","I can get three and six before ","I can get three and six before","I can get three and six bu","I can get three and six by adding three ","I can get three and six by adding","I can get three and six by addin","I can get three and six easily. Once You ","I can get three and six easily. Once You","I can get three and six easily. Once Yo","I can get three and six easily. Once Y","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subrta","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subrt","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subr","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zi","I can get three and six eas ily. Onc e you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zero. Then the pattern rem","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zero. Then the pattern repeats,","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zero. Then the pattern repeats. You can only get zero, three and x","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zero. Then the pattern repeats. You can only get zero, three and six","I can get three and six easily. Once you add three threes you get nine, and by subtracting nine you get zero. Then the pattern repeats. You can only get zero, three, and six."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":114437,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1099783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in wo rds how  you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five is nine, then subtract nine to get zero.","explanation_history":["One five gives five. Ad ","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subrtract","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subr","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven.","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven,  then su br","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two,","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve,","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Ther","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. The","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus  five ge ts six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus ni","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus n","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirti","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get thr ee. Thre e plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen ","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subract ","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subract","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight  plus fi ve gets thirteen, then subrac","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subra","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subr","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then  subtract  nine to get four. Four plus","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus nine ","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus nine","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to ge t three.  Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus nin","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus ni","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus n","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus  five ge ts seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five gets n","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five get","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five ge","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one.  One plu s five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five g","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five is nine, then subr","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four . Four p lus five is nine, then subtract no","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five is nine, then subtract nint","One five gives five. Add a five and you get ten, then subtract nine to get one. One plus five gets six. Six plus five gets eleven, then subtract nine to get two. Two plus five gets seven. Seven plus five gets twelve, then subtract nine to get three. Three plus five gets eight. Eight plus five gets thirteen, then subtract nine to get four. Four plus five is nine, then subtract nine to get zero."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":261379,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1361164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6  a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then subtract nine to get zero. If you reach zero in the pattern before getting all numbers, it is impossible to get any others. You only get six, three, and zero.","explanation_history":["Siz p","Siz ","Siz","Six plus six is ","Six plus six is twelve, then subr","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plux si","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plux s","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plux ","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plux","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, to get","Six plus six is twelve, the n subtra ct nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then se","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then sbu","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then sb","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then subtract nine to get zero. If you reach zero in the pate","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then subtract nine to get zero. If you reach zero in the pattern before r","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then subtract nine to get zero. If you reach zero in the pattern before getting all numbers, it is impossible to get any others. You only get six, three ","Six plus six is twelve, then subtract nine and you get three. Three plus six is nine, then subtract nine to get zero. If you reach zero in the pattern before getting all numbers, it  is impo ssible to get any others. You only get six, three, and zero."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":90936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1452101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":12105,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1464211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1"],"rt":13971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1478183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x","explain":true,"explanation":"Subtracting the element from n gives you a number that, when added to the element will be n. Then subtracting n from n will give you zero, the identity.","explanation_history":["Subr","Subtracting eht","Subtracting eh","Subtracting e","Subtracting the element from n ge","Subtracting the element from n gives you n","Subtracting the element from n gives you a number thea","Subtracting the element from n gives you a number the","Subtracting the element from n gives you a number that, when added to the element will be ne","Subtracting the element from n gives you a number that, when added to the element will be n. Then subrtracting ","Subtracting the elem ent from  n gives you a number that, when added to the element will be n. Then subtracting n from n wit","Subtracting the element from n gives you a number that, when added to the element will be n. Then subtracting n from n will give you zero, the identity."],"response_history":["n-x"],"rt":199201,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1677386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x, then x cannot be a generator, unless x is 1.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["X must not b","X must not ","If x is not one, it ","If x is n","If x is ","If x is","If x i","If x "," If x doe s not be","If x does not b","If x does not equal one","If x does not equal on","If x does not equal o","If x does not equal 1, then it mus ","If x does not equal 1, then it must not be a mu","If x does not equal 1, then it must not be a m","If x does not equal 1, then it must not be a de","If x does not equal 1, then it must not be a divisor of ","If x does not equal 1, then it must not be","If x does not equal 1, then it must not b","If x does not equal 1, then it must not ","If x does not equal 1, then it mu","If x does not equal 1, then it m","If x does not equal 1, then it ","If x does not equal 1, then it","If x does not equal 1, then i","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x i","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x ","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x, then x cannot be a generator.","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a mult iple of  x. If n is a multiple of x, then x cannot be a generator, unlees","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x, then x cannot be a generator, unlee","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x, then x cannot be a generator, unless e","If x does not equal 1, then n must not be a multiple of x. If n is a multiple of x, then x cannot be a generator, unless x is 1."],"rt":192557,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1869946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":27403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1897352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 4-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":4543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1901897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":11736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1913635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple o f a divi sor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of divisors of n would not be generators.","explanation_history":["If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. One ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. One","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. On","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. O","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every g","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would ba ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would ba","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would be a multipl e of "," If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would be a ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would be a","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would be ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would be","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would b","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Every non-generator x would at least be a multiple of 1 and itself, if not other ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiple  ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiple ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of the ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of the","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of th","If x in not  a genera tor, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of t","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of divisor ","If x in not a generator, then x must be a divisor of n. Some multiples of divisors of n would not be generators."],"response_history":["True","False","True","False"],"rt":285296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2198935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":75325,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2274262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</su b>, is x  +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Never","explain":true,"explanation":"x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a generator is x is not.","explanation_history":["x =","x +_n x is al","x +_n x is a","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to form a ","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to form a","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. It ","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. It","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If its","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If it","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generato r. If i","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a gern","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a ger","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a geera","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a geer","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a gee","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a generator t","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a generator ","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a generator, then ","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not a generator, th","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not ","x +_n x is a part of  the pat tern that you would use to test a generator. If x is not","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. ","x+_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. ","x+_nx is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. ","x+_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. ","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. You ","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. You","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. Yo","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. Y","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it coulb","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a j","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a gerner a","x +_ n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a gerner","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a gerne","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a gern","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a ger","x +_n x is a part of the pattern that you would use to test a generator. There is no way it could be a generator is x is not."],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":208429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2482693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":14414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2497109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1527,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2498637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["28"],"rt":2423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2501061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelo rs Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2504444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"pre-calculas","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["pre cac","pre cal","pre cacu","pre cac","pre calu","pre calculas","precalculas","pre-calculas"],"rt":16209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2520654,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the conc ept of m odular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2525494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - nev er heard  of it"],"rt":5542,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2531038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2534444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2912,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2537357,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3673,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2541032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":1948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2542982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Enl","English"],"rt":5022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2548006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":3710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2551718,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Too long","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Too long"],"rt":7134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2558853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]